Hello, today is the second day of Navratri and do you
know which goddess is worshipped on the second day?
Mother Goddess Brahmacharini is worshipped on the second day.
So the color of Mother Goddess Brahmacharini, which is the
color of today's Navratri, for the second day,
is
white. My shirt is not white, but today's
color is white, and white is the symbol of knowledge.
After that, the symbol of your learning is
white. So, today also, taking the
learning forward, we will talk about health
insurance and a plan of one company
and that is of
ICI Lombard. The
Health Advantage Plan of ICI Lombard is very good.
Today, like all the other videos that we have
published,
this is also a trending plan. Let's see its claim settlement rate. I have been
talking about claim settlement rate and claim income rate since the last video. So,
what is claim settlement rate? It is on 8859 of
ICI Lombard and INC rate.  At 91.6, means
last year a lot of claims were given,
hence the claim income was at 91.6.
You can join anytime between 18 to 65 years
and your dependent's age is 25
years, so you can join or get them to join.
It has a no claim bonus, every year at 20% the
no claim bonus will be up to 100%,
but yes once it reaches 100% it will
not reduce, so this is a good benefit, it is a
good thing and day care up to sum insurance,
you can take any day care treatment
up to the figure of sum insurance,
rest refill benefit, what are many other
plans, it gives unlimited refill or
restoration bonus, it gives ICLO's
health advantage, but it will give you only once,
next consumer bill, consumer bill coverage is
not included in this plan, if you
want to take a rider, then by taking a rider you can take the consumer
bill rider and you can avail that benefit.
Maternity benefit is not covered in this.
If you have gone to Global Hospital for a
trip or if you need
any hospitalization, then that is also
not covered in this.
Almost the last video was yesterday about Care. So, as much as
I said about the six or
seven different health insurance plans
that we have discussed so far, the
premium of ICCI's Health Advantage is quite low, and that of Manil Cigna is also
low,
and Care Care Supreme is also low. The
premium is a little higher normally, and that of Aago
and Niba Baba also has a slightly higher premium.
But if you want to take all the riders by adding these
riders, then
your gross expenditure will still be the same, which is Aago, that is,
Ler. So that's all for today. I hope
you enjoy the entire nine days of Navratri this year.
Analyze all the educational videos that we post on behalf of Aam Aadmi Ka Finance Pathshala and
take your financial decisions accordingly. Thank you.  Thank you so much,
like, share and subscribe, thank you.